A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Developing Countries Program, Program Staff Files FA528
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Developing Countries Program, Program Staff Files
1973-1987
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA528
2.4 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- Latin America Trustees Meeting, 1986 March; I
  - March 1986 (Box 1)
  - March 1986 (Box 1)
  - March 1986 (Box 1)
  - March 1986 (Box 1)
  - March 1986 (Box 1)
  - March 1986 (Box 1)
- Management Costs, II
  - FY 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - FY 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - FY 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - FY 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - FY 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - FY 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - FY 1982 -- Office of Latin America and the Caribbean -- Management Costs, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean -- Program Data Book -- Office for Peru, Bolivia and Ecuador, 1968-1970
- Elisa Scatena, III
  - Asia and Pacific Profiles, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Bangladesh Field Office, 1972 (Box 2)
  - International Division (ID) Reorganization, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Management Staff Profiles, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Vietnam Field Office Administration FY 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - Vietnam Field Office Administration FY 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
- Chika Iritani, IV
  - 1983 Chronological Correspondence (Box 2)
  - 1984 Chronological Correspondence (Box 2)
  - 1985 Chronological Correspondence (Box 2)
  - 1986 Chronological Correspondence (Box 2)
  - 1987 Chronological Correspondence (Box 2)